No!
Valon!
Can she even be revived after all that?
I've heard that it's been done before, but...
Hey, Laios? What are you...
The Resurrection Office. They'll know what to do.
Are you planning to take everything?
But aren't Wargbones mixed in there, too?
It's hard to tell them apart.
Let me help.
Please wait!
The link between the soul and body is fragile now.
You shouldn't move her.
The more damaged the body is, the weaker the soul's bond.
When a Resurrection fails, it's usually because the soul separated too far,
or because the body wasn't fully restored.
Then what should we do?
We go get a Revival Specialist and revive her here.
But the Restoration requires more than twice the amount of calories for the damaged parts,
so we'd also need to bring a lot of fresh meat for it to work.
It would rot on the way down, wouldn't it?
Hang on.
Huh?
Yes.
We have a large amount of fresh meat right here in front of us.
Hey, now hold on a sec.
You're gonna resurrect her with Dragon Meat?
Reviving isn't even your specialty.
I didn't want to scare anyone, so I never mentioned it.
What I specialize in is actually ancient magic, which is highly forbidden.
Its use is frowned upon, but using it to revive Falon, it's our best option.
Marcil!
Black magic?
That stuff is evil.
Magic doesn't have morality.
Well, Lyos, it's your choice.
Please do it, Marcil.
Bring my sister back from the dead.
All right, then.
I'll try.
Are you guys insane?
Using Dragon Meat, of all things.
Goat and pig are what people would normally use for this,
but we don't have that right now.
All right, let's start.
First things first, I would like to put the body back in its original shape,
so I'll start assembling her skeleton.
That makes sense.
I'm familiar with canine skeletons,
so I'll work on putting the wargs together.
That's kind of unnecessary, isn't it?
Not if it helps us avoid missing something or making dumb mistakes!
Humans have around 200 bones.
Then we're looking at about 840 bones total.
Huh?
How do you know that?
Dogs have around 320 bones,
and there are two skulls here,
so it's easy math.
Let's start with the most recognizable ones.
The rounder set is a human's ribcage,
and the spine is directly connected to the ribs.
Their curves don't look the same,
so they're easy to tell apart.
The toughest ones are the smaller bones from the hands and feet.
Yeah, it's a lot harder to tell the difference.
Let's start with the bigger pieces and work down.
This piece that I'm holding is the ankle bone.
Find the next biggest one,
then connect the two sides that line up,
and the instep is complete.
And then we have the bones from the hands.
Let's arrange them starting with the fingers.
I got it!
Like this, right?
So close.
Actually, the longest metacarpal,
despite what you might think,
goes on the pointer finger.
That just leaves us with the ones
that connect the fingers to the wrist.
Hint, please!
This isn't a game, Lyos!
There.
It's ready!
How do I put this?
What a beautiful skeleton.
Not bad for some bones.
Seems she had good calcium intake.
This isn't going to revive the wargs, too, is it?
Only human souls get bound to the dungeon.
Because otherwise,
this place would burst from all the monster souls.
All right.
Here we go.
And you guys are moving.
We will keep living.
Here we go.
Thank you.
I don't care.
Let's see.
I don't think.
Oh set.
Marcelle!
She just fainted.
So what happened?
Did it actually work?
Fallon!
Her airway's full of blood!
All right, just cough it out.
There, all good.
Fallon.
I'm glad you're safe.
You're cold.
Right! My armor, sorry.
Let me go get you some clothes.
Fallon, what's the matter?
You're feeling okay, right?
Good. I'm glad to hear it.
Marcel.
Marcel!
How's Fallon?
Alive and well.
But she's still a bit disoriented.
Fallon!
I'm so glad. Thank goodness.
Marcel.
Chill, Chuck.
How are you feeling?
She's still kind of confused about this.
All right. This guy here? His name's Senshi. He's been a big help during our journey.
Good to meet you, Fallon. I've heard a lot about you.
Senshi.
Seems like a good time to start prepping a meal.
Thank goodness. I was so worried, Fallon. I'm so happy. I bet everything worked out in the end.
Uh, Marcel?
Hmm?
I can wash myself, you know?
Yeah, but I wanted to make sure your skin was properly restored.
That tickles!
Yes.
Good.
Why is there a news here?
That's the mark I got from tripping and hitting the edge of the stairs when I was a little kid.
Oh, that's all?
Marcel.
You look even paler than I do.
That's because I don't have any mana.
If I eat something and get rest, I should be fi-
Huh?
What are you-
Sorry if I scared you. I was trying to give you some of my mana.
You don't have to do that. I don't even think you have enough to share with me right now, do you?
I actually feel good. Like there's power welling deep inside of me.
Fallon, you're still on the mend. So please, don't use magic until you're used to your body again.
I died, didn't I?
I... I don't really remember much about it.
What happened exactly?
You were all covered in wounds and...
For the red dragon to appear here...
Wait, are Shiro and Namaari okay?
I would feel just awful if anyone risked their lives and got hurt because of me.
No, they're all fine.
Also, that magic circle I saw...
There was something that just didn't feel right about it.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault you had to use something like that.
Stop worrying!
Sure, we ran into some hardships. Things got pretty rough.
But it's easy to look back and laugh at all that now.
Because everything turned out well in the end.
Fallon, there's no need for you to blame yourself.
No one regrets anything that we've been through.
As for that magic circle, things will be fine if we erase it.
For the moment...
Our biggest concern is how to safely get back home.
Oh! I still have to wash all my clothes.
And we still have to find you a new outfit.
Ugh, if it weren't for those stupid frogs.
There were frogs?
What do we do now?
Return to the surface.
We can't use return magic or the orcs' tunnels.
So we'll have to get to the castle from the main road.
Not what I meant.
You may have rescued your sister, but the fact remains that we're still broke.
I do have some savings in the bank, you know.
But no promissory note.
And it'll take a month to reproduce it.
Yeah, you're right.
So about that Marcel, the black magic she used.
Did you already know she had that ability?
I never asked her about the details.
But she had mentioned wanting to go into a dungeon to study it.
It always seemed weird to me.
An elf who looked like she was living pretty comfy wanting to go into a dungeon.
You don't suppose she's one of those dark elves, do you?
I don't want her causing any problems for us.
Who are you calling a dark elf?
If dark magic was harmless, it wouldn't be forbidden.
Oh yeah?
So you'd consider healing magic harmless?
Because even that can be used for torture.
I'm researching ways that forbidden magic can be useful to people.
And honestly, I'm not ashamed of it.
Although I think it's for the best if we forget about the method of resurrection this time around, if that's okay.
Didn't you just say that you weren't ashamed of it?
It's fine.
It's all over anyway.
I just realized.
Where'd Senshi go?
Maybe dealing with the dragon meat?
Oh, I just passed Mr. Senshi.
He was carrying a giant pan along with firewood.
Like I said, he's prepping food.
Food?
Near the dragon?
We've got to stop him!
What's happening?
When I cut open the dragon, I cut the fuel organ.
So lighting a fire close to it is gonna...
Senshi!
Please, stop!
He... he's alive.
Is this defensive magic?
Falon, did you cast that?
I think so.
How'd you do it so fast and without chanting?
I don't know.
I thought about needing to protect everyone.
And then...
That's amazing.
Is this that sudden heroic strength thing?
Sure would have been real helpful to have when we were fighting the red dragon.
Anyway, you were revived not that long ago, so please, refrain from using any more magic.
That startled me.
Didn't I say that dragons breathe fire from fuel they produce?
You ignited that fuel.
It's not going out, huh?
The fat inside the body is burning.
It'll die down eventually.
If that's the case, then I can't take the meat from in there.
Hmm, not good.
I guess I'll use that fire to cook.
Mix flour, yeast, salt, and water in a bowl and knead well.
Let it rest for a bit.
Go take a bath while it rests.
Shape it to your lichen as you stretch it out.
And add your choice of toppings.
Lightly sprinkle flour onto a piece of dragon hide.
Then place it inside the dragon.
Cut off the tip of the dragon's tail.
Ah, that's so wasteful!
Now skin it and place it in a soup.
Cut the meat into a block shape.
Place it on a heated scale, and after both sides are seared, dip it into some seasoning.
It's ready.
Oh, man.
Looks delicious.
Is this okay to eat?
Of course it isn't!
Tasty!
Feels like the first good meal I've eaten in a while.
Good, good.
Take your revenge on that dragon.
I guess it's fine.
I'm just glad that she's feeling better.
It's pretty tough.
The flavor seems kind of familiar.
Yeah, I can't really place it.
I don't think it's cow or pig, though.
If anything, it kind of tastes like...
It's a bit like living armor, isn't it?
Huh, you think so?
I don't taste the same rusty tinge the armor had.
The Kelpie and Frog were pretty soft, so maybe it's more like the basilisk?
What do you think, Lyos?
What are you all even talking about?
This color!
This firm texture!
The rich flavor!
Each of these things are distinctly unique!
So why are you comparing the taste of this to anything else?
Because this is the flavor of a dragon!
Uh, uh, Fallon, you may have realized by now, but...
We haven't had the resources to buy food, so we've been eating monsters...
So cool!
That is so cool!
What kind of monsters did you eat, and how did you eat them? Tell me!
Worried for nothing.
This is the worst possible outcome!
We ate a scorpion and a slime.
Even a walking mushroom.
No way! You did?
We harvested vegetables from some golems, too.
Wow! You ate a fish, man?
That wasn't... an option.
We did eat some living armor, though.
Huh? How'd you do that?
Let's see.
The armor is basically the outer shell.
And then, inside is a mollusk colony, which...
Wouldn't it be a lot faster to show her the real thing?
Huh?
What's this about?
Shh!
Huh?
Laius!
Why'd you keep this from us?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, adorable.
Can I touch?
Oh, it went back in.
It moves around on its own.
Seriously?
Sorry.
It was only supposed to tide me over until I found another weapon.
But it reacts to other monsters, which is convenient.
You were oddly perceptive at times.
Should have had Nomari appraise it for us.
In that situation, I probably would have also thought to hold onto it.
But tell everyone next time, if you lose the trust of those around you, you lose everything.
I won't do it again.
You have my word.
All right.
So what's your plan now?
I'd like to keep it until I get another weapon.
I can kill it if I submerge it in water.
But I'd have to break the sword to get it out, or it would just rot in there.
That's not good.
Guess we'll keep an eye on it.
Aren't you the one who said monsters are dangerous creatures?
And trust me, I haven't forgotten about that.
I figured after I'd made it harmless, I could just go on and use it however I felt like.
Well, I guess I was wrong.
It's too difficult to use monsters while they're still alive.
What does it taste like, brother?
Do you want to eat it?
Yes, please.
I'd love that.
There's doors all over this place, but seems like only two of them lead outside, huh?
No getting ambushed, at least.
This house seems like it'll be comfortable to live in.
Why do they have seven bathrooms, though?
All right, let's sleep here, then.
Yay!
It's been ages since I've slept in a real bed.
We still gotta use our sleeping bags, you know.
I'm sorry to be intruding like this.
Once we get enough rest, then we'll be on our way.
Hey, what's up?
A resident.
She's letting us stay.
Is that so?
That's great.
There are only four of them, so we'll have to share a sleeping bag.
We haven't really slept in the same bed since our school days, have we?
I wonder if we'll both fit.
I feel like I've probably gotten a lot taller since then, huh?
Oh, don't be so ridiculous!
I don't care if you've grown, you're still a runt in my eyes.
I'm glad that you're with us again.
Yeah, me too.
I'm gonna go say goodnight to my brother.
Brother?
What is it?
This injury here.
You were being reckless.
Why would you do...
Maybe if a certain sister of mine hadn't been reckless first, I wouldn't have even had that injury.
Huh?
So don't ever do anything like that again.
I honestly can't say I even recall what I...
I won't do it again.
Goodnight, big brother.
You too.
Sleep tight.
Huh?
You too.
Thank you.